A Guide to the Papers of Homer Stille Cummings, ca.1850-1955
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES III: CORRESPONDENCE OF THE ATTORNEY GENERAL AND POST-ATTORNEY GENERAL, 1933-1956
  - Statement re: Attorneys in U.S. Civil Service 1937 June (Box 196)
  - "Record of Legal Appointments between January 31, 1936 and December 31, 1937," arrangee by state 1938 February 10 (Box 196)
  - Transcript of a case, "United States of America vs. Aluminum Company of America" 1938 June 1-3, 3 copies; TMs (copy) (Box 196)
  - List of Executive Orders concerning the Department of Justice March 4, 1933-March 4, 1938, TMs (Box 196)
  - Summary of the Major Activities of the Department of Justice 4 March 1933-4 March 1938 (Box 196)
  - Memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings: "Classes of Material of Historical Value" n.d. [post 1938] (Box 196)
  - List of members of the Federal Judiciary appointed during the term of office of Homer Stille Cummings (4 March 1933-2 January 1939) with ratings ca. 1939 (Box 196)
  - Memoranda of Carl McFalrand to Homer Stille Cummings - Compilation of works by Homer Stille Cummings in the Library of Congress, compilations of appointments and cases in the Department of Justice, etc. ca. 1939 (Box 196)
  - Roster of members of the Federal Judiciary whose commissions were signed by Homer Stille Cummings, presented to him by Attorney General J. Howard McGrath 1951 August (Box 197)
  - Correspondence, Memoranda and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Gold Cases 1933-1934 (Box 197)
  - Memoranda and Papers re: Gold Cases, "For use at the White House" ca. 1934 October-ca. 1935 August (Box 197)
  - Correspondence, Memoranda and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Gold Cases 1934 October-December (Box 197)
  - Correspondence, Memoranda nad Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Gold Cases 1935 & n.d., 3 folders (Box 198)
  - Correspondence, Memoranda and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Gold Cases 1937-1938 & n.d. (Box 198)
  - Printed Material re: Gold Cases 1934-1935 (Box 198)
  - Rough Drafts of Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Plan for Judicial Reorganization, #2-5, 8, 10 n.d. [1937], 2 folders (Box 199)
  - Bills before Congress re: Judiciary includes Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Special Message on Judicial Reorganization 1937 January-July (Box 199)
  - Correspondence re: Judiciary - Alfred J. McClure, Jr. & William Denman 1935 February-1936 May-November (Box 199)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda re: Federal Judiciary - Possible reforms 1935 February-September; 1936 April-December (Box 199)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 January-August, 2 folders (Box 199)
  - Memoranda re: Retirement of aged Judges 1937 January (Box 200)
  - Memoranda re: Retirement of aged Judges, and Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judiciary Bill 1937 February (Box 200)
  - Memoranda re: Criticisms of Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 February-March (Box 200)
  - Memoranda re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 March (Box 200)
  - Memoranda by W.W. Gardner for the Solicitor General on the matter of Judicial Review and options for the President re: the Current Court 1937 March 6 (Box 200)
  - Report: Synopsis of responses (pro and con) to Homer Cummings' radio address supporting Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial reorganization plan (Box 200)
  - Memoranda re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 April-June (Box 200)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda re: Van Devanter resignation from Supreme Court and Concomitant vacancy 1937 May-August (Box 200)
  - Memoranda and Lists re: Supreme Court vacancies and possible appointments 1937 May-August, n.d. (Box 201)
  - Memoranda re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 July-August (Box 201)
  - Correspondence, Notes, and Articles re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan in retrospect 1937 August-1952 July (Box 201)
  - Memoranda re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan n.d. [1937] (Box 201)
  - Memoranda re: Historical Analysis of Supreme Court Decisions n.d. [1937] (Box 201)
  - Memoranda recounting the historic role of the Supreme Court in the American system n.d. [1937] (Box 201)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1939 July-August (Box 201)
  - Debates in Congress re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 January-February (Box 202)
  - Hearings and Debates in Congress re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 March 8-April 17 (Box 202)
  - "Summary Analysis of Testimony, Pro and Con," Committee on the Judiciary, U.S. Senate, Hearings on S. 1392, Reorganization of the Federal Judiciary 1937 March 10-April 23, TMs (Box 202)
  - Hearings and Debats in Congress re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937, 4 folders (Box 203)
  - Speech of David J. Lewis re: Judicial Veto 1935 August (Box 203)
  - Addresses and Journal article re: the Judiciary 1936-1937 (Box 203)
  - Statements and Speeches favorable to Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 February-March 10, 2 folders (Box 203)
  - Statements and Speeches favorable to Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 March 11-31 (Box 204)
  - Statements and Speeches unfavorable to Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 March, May (Box 204)
  - Statements and speeches favorable to Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 April (Box 204)
  - Statements and Speeches favorable to Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan n.d. [1937] (Box 204)
  - Research Material: Memoranda re: Justices' Decisions and other items 1937 March; n.d. (Box 204)
  - Research Material: Attorney General's Review of Court Injunctions 1937 March 25 (Box 204)
  - Research Material: Lists and Graph on Supreme Court Justices and Decisions 1937; n.d. (Box 204)
  - Research Material: Summary of REferendum Vote by members of the Bar on Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 April (Box 204)
  - Research Material: Data re: Age and Tenure of Federal Judges n.d. [1937] (Box 204)
  - Research Material: Episodes in American history re: the Judiciary 1787-1875 (Box 204)
  - Research Material: Files on Reform of the Judiciary - Precedents in the form of Hearings, Bills, and Laws 1869-1895; 1906-1936, 3 folders (Box 205)
  - Research Material: W.C. Abbott, Irving Babbit et. al. on Democracy and its Discontents ca. 1922-1930 (Box 205)
  - Research Material: Will Durant, Rowland Egger et. al. on Democracy and its Discontents ca. 1922-1930 (Box 205)
  - Research Material: Quotations from Justice Holmes, Charles Beard and the New York Times re: the Supreme Court ca. 1935-1937 (Box 205)
  - Research Material: The problem of aged Judges - The Canadian Response [ca. 1937] (Box 205)
  - Research Material: American Presidents on the Judiciary - Jefferson 1937, n.d. (Box 206)
  - Research Material: the problem of aged judges - English precedents n.d. (Box 206)
  - Research Material: American Presidents on the Judiciary - John Quincy Adams, Andrew Jackson, Martin Van Buren, Abraham Lincoln n.d. (Box 206)
  - Research Material: American Presidents on the Judiciary - Grant, Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, Woodrow Wilson n.d. (Box 206)
  - Research Material: American Political Leaders on the Judiciary - John Marshall, Daniel Webster, F.P. Blair, Stephen Douglas, C.E. Hughes n.d. (Box 206)
  - Pamphlets re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan, includes Law Journal articles 1937 February-March (Box 206)
  - Pamphlets re: Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 February-March (Box 206)
  - Pamphlets re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan, includes Law Journal articles (includes memorandum) 1937 April-June, 2 folders (Box 206)
  - Newspaper Clippings re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1937 January-July, 4 folders (Box 207)
  - Newspaper Clippings re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan n.d. [1937] (Box 207)
  - Newspaper Clippings re: Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Judicial Reorganization Plan 1941 September (Box 207)
- SERIES IV: SPEECHES, 1886-1950 & ARTICLES, 1918-1945
  - Speeches by Homer Stille Cummings re: Senator Copeland and the World Court and other topics n.d. (Box 207)
  - Speeches by Homer Stille Cummings: "Robert Fulton" 1886 January 21 (Box 207)
  - Speeches by Homer Stille Cummings: "Buffalo" 1888 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings entitled "Political Speeches" 1888-1892 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Bolivar" 1889 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "An Author's Personality" 1889 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Hunting" 1889 January 28 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Clerk's Tale" 1890 March 9 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "William III of England" 1890 June 2 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "War" 1891 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "American Fiction" 1891 May 5 (Box 207)
  - Speeches by Homer Stille Cummings at Yale Law School re: "World's Fair and Law School Policy" ca. 1892-1893 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the Democratic Party and the Gold Standard 1896 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the Silver Standard 1896 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Merrill Business College, Stamford, Conn. 1897 April 30 (Box 207)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Connecticut Congress of Mothers 1901 April 17 (Box 208)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the New Canaan Centennial Celebration 1901 June 19 (Box 208)
  - Newspaper copies of Homer Stille Cummings' speech at the New Canaan Centennial 1901 June 21 (Box 208)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "William McKinley" 1901 September 22 (Box 208)
  - Notes for a speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Rippowam Lodge 1901 November 25 (Box 208)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: Anti-Trust and Monopoly 1902 (Box 208)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the Democratic Platform 1902 (Box 208)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Catholic Club of Norwalk 1903 February 12 (Box 208)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: Monument Address before the Eagles 1906 May 6 (Box 208)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Suburban Club 1907 April 6 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at a banquet honoring Mr. Bryan 1907 November 29 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Memorial Day Services, Stamford Elks 1907 December 1 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: Memorial Address before the Stamford Elks 1907 December 1 (Box 209)
  - Notes for a speech by Homer Stille Cummings before Y.P.C.U. 1908 April 5 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: Memorial Address before Danbury Elks Club 1909 December 5 (Box 209)
  - Notes for a speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the Democratic Campaign in Connecticut 1910 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the Democratic Party Platform ca. 1910-1914 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before a banquet honoring Judge George Wheeler 1910 September 29 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Abraham Lincoln" 1912 February 14 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Yale Alumni Association 1912 February 23 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Democratic State Convention, held in Hartford, Conn. 1912 September 11 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Derby" 1913 January 20 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Robert Burns" 1913 January 24 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Abraham Lincoln" 1913 February 9 (Box 209)
  - Speech (poem) by Homer Stille Cummings before the Catholic Club 1913 February 13 (Box 209)
  - Speech (notes) by Homer Stille Cummings: "Thomas Jefferson" 1913 April 12 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before Manufacturers Association, Scranton, Pennsylvania 1915 June 12 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: Commencement Address, Stamford, Connecticut 1915 June 17 (Box 209)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Robert Burns" 1916 January 27 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Democratic State Convention, New Haven, Connecticut 1916 May 9 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings accepting the Democratic nomination for the United States Senate for Connecticut 1916 September 20 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Stamford Theatre re: America's neutrality 1916 November 2 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Conduct of a National Political Campaign" 1917 February 4 (Box 210)
  - Notes for a speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Yale University re: party politics 1920 March 22 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Democratic National Convention, San Francisco 1920 June 28 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Jefferson Day Banquet Allegheny County Democratic Committee, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania re: the international policies of Woodrow Wilson 1921 April 11 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Popular Reactions in the Struggle Toward Peace" 1921 November 22 (Box 210)
  - Memoranda re: Clemenceau 1922 November 21 (Box 210)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Commencement Exercises of the University of Virginia 1923 June 12 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Liberty and Law" 1923 June 17 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Citizen and the Law" 1923 October 31 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Duty of the Citizen," at the New England Citizenship Conference 1924 January 21 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "William G. McAdoo, 'America's Foremost Progressive Democrat'" 1924 February 18 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Some Suggestions with Reference to the Political Situation" 1924 March 24 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the State Democratic Committee banquet of New Hampshire re: the principles at the Democratic Party 1924 June 11 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: Presidential Election and the Democratic Party 1924 October (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the Democratic Campaign in Connecticut in 1924 1924 December 16 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the complimentary dinner held in his honor by the Fairfield County Bar 1925 February 12 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Contact with Life through the Law" by Homer Stille Cummings before the Kentucky State Bar Association 1925 July 1 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "A Plea for the World Court" 1925 December 3 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Character of Abraham" 1926 February 14 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Travelling in Spain" 1926 November 23 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Bridgeport Elks re: Fraternal Organizations 1926 December 5 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "George Washington" 1927 February 20 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before Petroleum Heat and Power Company Banquet 1928 August 28 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: Water Power 1928 October 24 (Box 211)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Catholic Club, Norfolk, Connecticut 1929 February 12 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Civic Pride" 1929 December (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Progress Toward Peace" 1930 April 25 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: Keynote Address at the Connecticut Democratic State Convention 1930 September 30 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: "Equality of Opportunity" 1930 October 30 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at a testimonial dinner given to Chief Justice George W. Wheeler 1930 December 12 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the McNeil Banquet 1932 March (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings seconding the nomination of Franklin Delano Roosevelt at the Democratic National Convention in Chicago 1932 June 30 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the failure of the Hoover administration 1932 October (?) (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings re: the 1932 Presidential Campaign 1932 November 5 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings for use during Presidential Campaign of 1932 1932 (Box 212)
  - Speech (excerpts) by Homer Stille Cummings at a dinner given in his honor, Stratfield Hotel, Bridgeport, Connecticut 1933 April 15 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Crime in High Places" 1933 April 24 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Department of Justice and the New Deal" 1933 June 10 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Modern Tendencies and the Law" 1933 August 31 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Predatory Crime" 1933 September 11 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Recurring Problem of Crime" 1933 October 12 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Campaign Against Crime" 1933 November 22 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Law Enforcement" 1934 January 10 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Education, Science, and the New Deal" 1934 February 26 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Democratic Problems for the Bar" 1934 March 14 (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Liberty Under Law and Administration," White lecture at the University of Virginia Law School 1934 April 16, 2 folders (Box 212)
  - 3 speeches by Homer Stille Cummings: "Liberty under Law and Administration," by Homer Stille Cummings at the University of Virginia Law school under the auspices of the William H. White Foundation [1934] (Box 212)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "A Twelve Point Program" 1934 April 19 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Attorney Genteral Cummings Outlines Crime Prevention Program Over CBS" 1934 April 19 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "How the Government Battles Organized Lawlessness" 1934 May 12 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Our Widening Life" 1934 May 27 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Wisdom of the Young" 1934 June 9 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Banquet of the Federal Bar Association re: Law 1934 June 25 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Law and the New Deal" 1934 July 6 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Law and the Prophets" 1934 July 9 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Commonwealth Club of California re: Crime 1934 August 17 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Lessons of the Lindbergh Case" 1934 September 22 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Menace of Organized Crime" 1934 September 26 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Government's Program to Fight Lawlessness" 1934 October 13 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Dedication of the Department of Justice Building" 1934 October 25 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Stamford, Connecticut re: "Economy" 1934 October 30 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "America's Tribute of Farewell to Evangeline Booth" 1934 November 1 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings as the president's reprasentative at the Convocation honoring William Cardinal O'Connell 1934 November 14 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Attorney General's Conference on Crime 1934 December 10 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Lessons of the Crime Conference" 1934 December 13 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Co-ordination of Law Enforcement in the Movement against Crime" 1935 January 14 (Box 213)
  - Interview between Homer Stille Cummings and Davidson Taylor (C.B.S.) 1935 March 4 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings under the auspices of the World Narcotic Defense Association re: International Drug Legislation 1935 March 21 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Control of Narcotics" 1935 March 22 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Criminal Law Administration, its Problems and Developments" 1935 April 15 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Problem of Youth" 1935 April 20 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Education and Training for Public Service" 1935 May 4 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Washignton-Connecticut Day Dinner 1935 May 25 (Box 213)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Pioneers" 1935 June 3 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Conference of the Fourth Judicial Circuit of the U.S. 1935 June 6 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Progress towards a National program for the Prevention, Detection, and Punishment of Crime" 1935 June 7 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Imperial Council, A.A.O.N.M.S. 1935 June 11 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Justice" 1935 June 19 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Annual Convention of the International Association of Chiefs of Police 1935 July 8 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Police Training School of the Department of Justice" 1935 July 25 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Organized Religion and Crime Prevention" 1935 August 29 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Crime Problem at Home and Abroad" 1935 October 28 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Crime and its Problems" 1935 October 28 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Hotel Taft, New Haven, Connecticut re: Economic Recovery 1935 November 9 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "World Peace Ways Program" 1935 November 21 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The American Constitutional Method" 1935 December 18 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings before the Masonic Forum re: Crime 1936 April 3 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Progress Toward a Modern Administration of Criminal Justice in the United States" 1936 April 27 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: Keynote address to the Connecticut Democratic Convention 1936 May 15 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Dedication of the New Law School Building, Washington and Lee University 1936 June 11 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings seconding the nomination of President Roosevelt at the Democratic Convention 1936 June 26 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Independence Day Ceremonies, Society of Tammany 1936 July 4 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "Two Bureaus" 1936 August 6 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Governor's Day, Springfield, Ill. re: Economic recovery 1936 August 20 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "The Attorney General's Survey of Release Procedures" 1936 August 25 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings presiding officer at the American Bar Association meeting 1936 August 26 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings: "A Nation was Brought into Being" 1936 September 17 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at the Lyric Theatre, Bridgeport re: Campaign 1936 October 23 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Majestic Tehatre, Peoria, Ill., re: Budget 1936 October 26 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Book-Cadillac Hotel, Detroit, Michigan re: Campaign 1936 October 27 (Box 214)
  - Speech by Homer Stille Cummings at Moose Hall, Lancaster, Pennsylvania re: Campaign 1936 October 29 (Box 214)